关系弄清楚了。但是我们仍然没有数据库
Now that's a contract. But we still don't have a database.
我们的数据库类会继承一个安卓类-—SQLITEOpenHELPER
Our database class will extend an Android class. SQLITEOpenHELPER.
SQLITEOpenHELPER有很强力的工具来帮我们处理数据库版本
SQLITEOpenHELPER contains cool stuff to help us handle database versioning.
当我们以后修改数据库时，它会帮助我们修改表
As we make changes to our database in the future, it will help us modify our
对于很多App，能在更新版本时不丢失数据是非常关键的
tables. For many apps, being able to upgrade to a new version without data loss
让我们来data包中创建一个继承SQLITEOpenHelper
is critical. Let's create a WeatherDBHelper class within the data package and
的WeatherDBHelper类
have that extend SQLite Open Helper. [SOUND] We can add
我们能通过Ctrl+I快捷键添加所需函数
the required methods by hitting Ctrl+I.
然后按Ctrl+O来覆写构造器，把这些变量
And we can override the constructor by hitting Ctrl+O. So now we can hard code
硬编码。硬编码name为我们的DATABASE_NAME
these variables to constructor. Hard coding name to database name,
factory改为null，version改成DATABASE_VERSION
our factory to null, and our version to database version.
你可以看到我将DATABASE_NAME设为了公共常量（public）
Now, you'll note I have made the database name public, and
这是为了我们之后的测试用
that's because we're going to use it in our tests in the future.
我们在下面有了onCreate()和onUpgrade()方法
Now you see we've got it on create and an onUpgrade method.
在onCreate()中，我们准备用WeatherContract中的数据来
In the OnCreate method, we're going to start by creating a string to build
构造一个字符串来完成天气的表
the weather entry table using data defined within the weather entry contract.
我在这儿加一个注释，这样你就知道待会儿要回到哪里来
Now I'm just going to add this comment, so you know where to go back and
加上地点的那些东西了。因为天气条目是取决于地点条目的
add the location entry stuff later. Since weather entry depends on
我通常会先写好地点条目
location entry, I would normally write location entry first, but
但是天气条目非常复杂。所以更好的做法是我解释下我们在做什么
weather entry is pretty complicated. So I'd rather explain what we've done and
然后将地点条目交给你们写。我们准备用原始SQL
leave location entry up to you. We're going to use raw SQL for
来创建表，从表名开始
our create table query, beginning with the table name from our contract.
这时候，我们应该先导入WeatherContract.locationentry和
At this point, it's helpful to import WeatherContract.locationentry and
WeatherContract.weatherentry。这会使我们的SQL语句更容易读懂。我们从
weather entry. It makes our query so much easier to read. We'll start with
ID开始，将它设置为自增主键
our ID field, which we'll set as our primary key in an auto increment field.
注意下整数（integer）在SQLite中是一个有符号并且最长8字节的数
Note that integer is actually a signed value up to eight bytes long in SQLite.
用自增功能，不过这可能和你想的有点不同
Using the auto increment feature doesn't do precisely what one might think.
设置ID作为一个整数主键实际上使
Setting up the ID is an integer primary key actually makes
这个值变得独一无二，但是它可能不是总是增长的
the value unique whenever you do an insert, but it may not always increment.
它可能会重复利用记录已经被删除的已存在的ID值
It may reuse existing ID values of the records have been deleted.
而自动增长的有用之处在于，有时候你会用两种方式
What autoincrement is really useful for, is if you're synchronizing data two
与服务器同步数据。但是，在这儿我们会用上它，因为它会使
ways with the server. But, we'll take advantage of it here because it makes data
数据排列得更加自然，因为我们是以从服务器上取回来的顺序
from our queries sort a bit more naturally because we insert them in the right
来插入它的。我们在字段上添加了点约束条件
order coming from the server. In general, we're using constraints on fields.
在这里不是null。这么做的原因是会让数据库替我们做些
In this case, not null. We do this because it allows the database to do much of
参数验证。这样做有个缺点，
our parameter validation for us. The tricky part about doing it this way,
当约束失败时我们得不到有用的错误信息
is that we don't get useful errors when these constraints fail, so
所以对debug是一个挑战。我们在日期这
it can be challenging to debug. We're using a human readable string for
用一个可读性强的字符串。这么做没什么问题
the date. There's no strong reason for or
我们希望尽量简化查询
against this choice. We wanted to normalize the date to simplify our queries,
并且尽量增强可读性。从open weather服务器取得的日期
and human readability simplifies debugging. The date comes from open weather in
是Unix时间格式，里面有些信息我们需要去除掉
Unix time stamp format with some time information that we need to get rid of.
我不准备每个字段都详细讲。REAL在SQL中代表浮点
I'm not going to cover every field. Real means floating point in SQL.
用不动点整数很好
It would have been fine to have used integer with fixed point math as well and
有些人还说这会更快
some would argue that this would be faster, but
但是REAL在这里因为我们存储用了浮点值，所以更直观
real is more straight forward since we're storing floating point values. Now for
有趣的部分来了，我们来设置一个LOC_KEY
the fun stuff, we're going to set up a loc key.
这是与你要创建的地点条目表不相关的一个键
It's a foreign key to the location entry table that you will be building.
SQLite用它来增强表之间的联系
This causes SQLite to enforce the relationship between the tables.
我们不能在没有相关地点条目的时候增加一个天气条目
We cannot insert a weather entry when there is no corresponding location entry.
并且我们不能在仍然有天气条目依赖于地点条目的时候，删除这个地点条目
And we cannot delete a location entry if there are still weather entries that
很酷，对不对？最后一个约束条件
depend on it. Cool stuff, right? One last constraint.
我们的日期文本加上地点必须是独一无二的。如果冲突了，取代这个数据
Our date text plus location must be unique. On conflict, replace the data.
这让我们从open weather API添加数据更轻松
This allows us to insert new data from the open weather API easily.
当天气预报改变时，保留已有的键然后更新值
Preserving existing keys and updating the value as the forecast changes.